Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - R
        - R. Type - Love is blind; Heaven, 1994; SR-22053; R. Type; Ant-Head Norris (Box 403)
          Catalog # HPY 012; A-side Matrix # HPY 012 A
          Hyper Records
          United Kingdom
        - R-Angels - Left to right, 2000; SR-22054; R-Angels (Box 403)
          Catalog # MOTR 20108-1; A-side Matrix # MOTR-20103-1A
          Motown
          New York, New York
        - R-Fresh - Keep rockin, 1998; SR-22055; R-Fresh; Devastata (Box 403)
          Catalog # RF001; A-side Matrix # RF001-A
          Fresh Productions
          Florida, United States
        - R-Kidz - Full moon; Possessed, 1998; SR-22056; R-Kidz (Box 403)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # HAND 046T; A-side Matrix # HAND046 T A-01-1
          Hard Hands
          London, United Kingdom
        - R&R - Raw jointz, SR-22057; R&R (Box 403)
          Catalog # AV127; A-side Matrix # AV-127-A
          AV8
        - Ra-Kapone - Down with the black mob; Never under pressure, 1995; SR-22058; Ra-Kapone (Box 403)
          Catalog # D.D.-0011; A-side Matrix # DD0012A
          D&D Records
          United States
        - Rabbit in the Moon - FlooRi.D.A. (disc one), 1999; SR-22059; Rabbit in the Moon (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22060. Double album.
          Catalog # HAL 009; A-side Matrix # HAL-009-A2
          Hallucination
          Tampa, Florida
        - Rabbit in the Moon - FlooRi.D.A. (disc two), 1999; SR-22060; Rabbit in the Moon (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22059. Double album.
        - Rabin, Trevor - Can't look away, 1989; SR-22061; Rabin, Trevor (Box 403)
          Promo
          Catalog # 60781-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E 60781 A DMM-1 SP1-1
          Elektra
        - Race - Show me the way, 1982; SR-22062; Race (Box 403)
          Catalog # DMD 379; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-43791-1
          Atlantic
        - Rachabane, Barney - Blow Barney blow, 1985; SR-22063; Rachabane, Barney (Box 403)
          Catalog # JDI-9359; A-side Matrix # JDI 9359-SA-ES2
          Jive Afrika
        - Rachele - Dirty movies, 1983; SR-22064; Rachele (Box 403)
          Catalog # SOS 1448EP; A-side Matrix # SOS-1448EP-1
          SOS Records
        - Rachele - Dirty movies, 1983; SR-22065; Rachele (Box 403)
        - Rachele - Dirty movies, 1983; SR-22066; Rachele (Box 403)
        - Rachid - Pride, 1998; SR-22067; Rachid (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22068. 2 copies.
          Catalog # U8P 1266; A-side Matrix # U8P-1266 A
          Universal Records
        - Rachid - Pride, 1998; SR-22068; Rachid (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22067. 2 copies.
        - Racionais MC's - Raio x Brasil, 1993; SR-22069; Racionais MC's (Box 403)
          Catalog # ZB0015; A-side Matrix # ZB-0015-A
          Zimbabwe Records
          Sao Paulo, Brazil
        - Radikal Doodz - Caton Park kool out, 1993; SR-22070; Radikal Doodz (Box 403)
          Catalog # M-004; A-side Matrix # M-004-A
          Mission Recordz
          Albany, New York
        - Radikal Doodz - Caton Park kool out, 1993; SR-22071; Radikal Doodz (Box 403)
        - Radio - Groovin', 1994; SR-22072; Radio; DarQ (Box 403)
          Catalog # DMD 2164; A-side Matrix # STDM-73809-73121-73808-1
          Interscope Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - Radio Heart - London times, 1987; SR-22073; Radio Heart; Numan, Gary (Box 403)
          Contains a 7" promo flexi-disc
          Catalog # GFMT 112; A-side Matrix # GFMT-112-A-1
          GFM Records
        - Radio Heart - Radio heart, 1987; SR-22074; Radio Heart; Numan, Gary (Box 403)
          Catalog # GFMT 109; A-side Matrix # GFN (T)-109-1A
        - Rae & Christian - Northern sulphuric soul (disc one), 1998; SR-22075; Rae & Christian; Jeru the Damaja (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22076. Double album.
          Catalog # GCLP004; A-side Matrix # GCLP 104 A-01-01
          Grand Central Records
          Manchester, United Kingdom
        - Rae & Christian - Northern sulphuric soul (disc two), 1998; SR-22076; Rae & Christian; Jeru the Damaja (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22075. Double album.
          Catalog # GCLP004; A-side Matrix # GCLP 104 C-01-01
        - Rae & Christian - Northern sulphuric soul (4-song sampler), 1998; SR-22077; Rae & Christian; Jeru the Damaja (Box 403)
          Catalog # SM-9084 DJ; A-side Matrix # SM-9084-A
          Sm:)e Communications
        - Rae, Jesse - Rusha; Desire, 1982; SR-22078; Rae, Jesse (Box 403)
          Catalog # 44-03374; A-side Matrix # XXS-170704-1A
          Columbia
        - Rae, Kym - Just be good to me, 1996; SR-22079; Rae, Kym; Father MC (Box 403)
          Catalog # SRI 1001; A-side Matrix # SRI-1001 A
          Situation Records
          Teaneck, New Jersey
        - Raeburn, Boyd - Jewells (disc one), 1980; SR-22080; Raeburn, Boyd (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22081. Double album.
          Catalog # SJL 2250; A-side Matrix # SJL-2250 A-1
          Savoy Records
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Raeburn, Boyd - Jewells (disc two), 1980; SR-22081; Raeburn, Boyd (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22080. Double album.
          Catalog # SJL 2250; A-side Matrix # SJL-2250 C-1
        - Raekwon - The hood; Clientele kidd, 2003; SR-22082; Raekwon; Villarreal, Tiffany (Box 403)
          Catalog # UNIR 21065; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20165-1A
        - Raekwon - Live from NY; Power, 1999; SR-22083; Raekwon (Box 403)
          Catalog # RPROLP4315; A-side Matrix # ROROLP-4315 A
          Loud Records
        - Chef Raekwon - Ice cream, 1995; SR-22084; Chef Raekwon; Raekwon (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22085. 2 copies. Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # RDAB 64418; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64418-1-A1
        - Chef Raekwon - Ice cream, 1995; SR-22085; Chef Raekwon; Raekwon (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22084. 2 copies.Promo
        - Chef Raekwon - Immobilarity (disc one), 1999; SR-22086; Chef Raekwon; Raekwon (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22087. Double Album.
          Catalog # C2 63844; A-side Matrix # 62225 AL
        - Chef Raekwon - Immobilarity (disc two), 1999; SR-22087; Chef Raekwon; Raekwon (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22086. Double Album.
          Catalog # C2 63844; A-side Matrix # 62226 AL
        - Raes - I only wanna get up and dance, 1979; SR-22088; Raes (Box 403)
          Catalog # SP 17064; A-side Matrix # SP-17111
          A&M Records
          Scarborough, Ontario
        - Rage Against the Machine - Bullet in the head, 1993; SR-22089; Rage Against the Machine (Box 403)
          Catalog # ZAS 5195; A-side Matrix # XSS-5195A-1
          Epic Associated
        - Ragga Twins - Hooligan 69, 1991; SR-22090; Ragga Twins (Box 403)
          Catalog # SUAD 16; A-side Matrix # SUAD-16-A
          Shut Up and Dance Records
        - Ragga Twins - Reggae owes me money (LP sample), 1991; SR-22091; Ragga Twins (Box 403)
          Catalog # SUADLP002S; A-side Matrix # SUAD LP 002 A
        - Raggafunk - Come and get me, 1990; SR-22092; Raggafunk; Overlord X (Box 403)
          Catalog # 537 841-0 DJ; A-side Matrix # 162-537-841-0-A-SP
          Mango
        - Rags & Riches - Medley: el watusi/ la bamba, 1983; SR-22093; Rags & Riches (Box 403)
          Catalog # NBD 20247; A-side Matrix # NBD20247-82.CS.390-PRC.C-1-1
          Casablanca
        - Rags & Riches - Land of 1,000 dances, 1983; SR-22094; Rags & Riches (Box 403)
          Catalog # 422-810 335-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # 422-810-335-1-AS-PRC-C-1-1
        - Rah Digga - Break fool, 2000; SR-22095; Rah Digga (Box 403)
          Catalog # ED-6219; A-side Matrix # STED-6215A
        - Rah Digga - Dirty Harriet (disc one), 2000; SR-22096; Rah Digga; Busta Rhymes (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22097. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # ED-6203; A-side Matrix # STE-62476-1A
        - Rah Digga - Dirty Harriet (disc two), 2000; SR-22097; Rah Digga; Busta Rhymes (Box 403)
          In same jacket as # SR-22096. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # ED-6203; A-side Matrix # STE-62476-1C
        - Rah Digga - Break fool, 2000; SR-22098; Rah Digga (Box 403)
        - Rah Digga - Party over here, 2003; SR-22099; Rah Digga; Lloyd Banks (Box 403)
          Catalog # 82876-53336-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-53336-1-A
          J Records
        - Raheem - Dance floor, 1988; SR-22100; Raheem (Box 403)
          Catalog # SP-12278; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012278-A
          Santa Monica, California
        - Rahsun - I'll be around, 1998; SR-22101; Rahsun; 4 Deep (Box 403)
          Catalog # BAS 41230; A-side Matrix # XSS-41230-A
          550 Music
        - Raiders of the Lost Art - Back in the day, 1993; SR-22102; Raiders of the Lost Art (Box 403)
          Catalog # DMD 2018; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-65867-65868-1
          Big Beat
        - Rain - Let the beat, SR-22103; Rain (Box 403)
          Catalog # BEAT 01; A-side Matrix # BEAT-01-A
        - Rainbow Brite - Paint a rainbow in your heart, 1984; SR-22104; Rainbow Brite (Box 403)
          Catalog # 62523; A-side Matrix # 62523-KMPRC-984-SIDE 1
          Buena Vista Records
          Burbank, California
        - Rainbow Girls - Make your move for love, 1990; SR-22105; Rainbow Girls (Box 403)
          Catalog # VL 15134-1; A-side Matrix # 15134-A
          Quality Records
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Rainer - Nod to N2O, 1996; SR-22106; Rainer (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22107. Different discs. Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # X002; A-side Matrix # X002 A
          X Records
        - Eazy-E - Just tah let u know, 1995; SR-22107; Eazy-E; MC Ren (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22106. Different discs.
          Catalog # 88561-5532-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-5532-1A
          Ruthless Records
        - Rainmen - Pas d'chilling, 1998; SR-22108; Rainmen; Fonky Family (Box 404)
          Catalog # VVR5005746; A-side Matrix # VVR 5005746 A
          V2
          Canada
        - Raise the Dragon - Deliverance, 1984; SR-22109; Raise the Dragon (Box 404)
          Catalog # SP-70508; A-side Matrix # SP 070508-A
          I.R.S. Records
          Universal City, California
        - Raja-Neé - Walking away with it, 1994; SR-22110; Raja-Neé (Box 404)
          Catalog # 31458 7491 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 7491 1A
          Perspective Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Raketen - The sound für zwischendurch, 2003; SR-22111; Raketen (Box 404)
          Catalog # FRM002; A-side Matrix # B379622-01 A1
          Freundschaft Musik
          Germany
        - Rakim - When I be on tha mic; Flow forever, 1999; SR-22112; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22113; SR-22114. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # U8P 1634; A-side Matrix # U8P-1634 1A
        - 504 Boyz - Wobble wobble, 2000; SR-22113; 504 Boyz; Master P (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22112; SR-22114. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # 08724-81350-15; A-side Matrix # 08724-81350-1-A
          No Limit Records
          New Orleans, Louisiana
        - 504 Boyz - Wobble wobble, 2000; SR-22114; 504 Boyz; Master P (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22112; SR-22113. 2 copies.Promo
        - Rakim - The 18th letter (disc one), 1997; SR-22115; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22116. Double album.
          Catalog # U2-53113; A-side Matrix # U2 53113 A
        - Rakim - The 18th letter (disc two), 1997; SR-22116; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22115. Double album.
          Catalog # U2-53113; A-side Matrix # U2 53113 C
        - Rakim - The 18th letter (disc one), 1997; SR-22117; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22118. Double album.
        - Rakim - The 18th letter (disc two), 1997; SR-22118; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22117. Double album.
        - Rakim - The master (disc one), 1999; SR-22119; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22120. Double album.
          Catalog # 314542082-1; A-side Matrix # U8P-1674-A
        - Rakim - The master (disc two), 1999; SR-22120; Rakim; Rahzel (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22119. Double album.
          Catalog # 314542082-1; A-side Matrix # U8P-1674-C
        - Rakim - When I be on tha mic; Flow forever, 1999; SR-22121; Rakim (Box 404)
        - Rakim - The saga begins, 1997; SR-22122; Rakim (Box 404)
          Catalog # U8P 1260; A-side Matrix # U8P-1260-A
        - Rakim - Guess who's back (remixes), 1997; SR-22123; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22124. 2 copies.
          Catalog # U8P-1240; A-side Matrix # U8P-1240 A
        - Rakim - Guess who's back (remixes), 1997; SR-22124; Rakim (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22123. 2 copies.
        - Rakim - All night long; Uplift, 2000; SR-22125; Rakim (Box 404)
          Catalog # U8P-1664; A-side Matrix # U8P-1664-A
        - Rakim - The book of life (Eric B. & Rakim's greatest hits) (disc one), 1997; SR-22126; Rakim; Eric B. (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22127. Double album.
          Catalog # U2-53117; A-side Matrix # U2-53117-1-A
        - Rakim - The book of life (Eric B. & Rakim's greatest hits) (disc two), 1997; SR-22127; Rakim; Eric B. (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22126. Double album.
          Catalog # U2-53117; A-side Matrix # U2-53117-2-A
        - Rally Ral - Something kinda funky, 1994; SR-22128; Rally Ral; E-A-Ski (Box 404)
          Catalog # SPRO 50794; A-side Matrix # PVL-53158-A
          Priority Records
        - Rally Ral - Something kinda funky, 1994; SR-22129; Rally Ral; E-A-Ski (Box 404)
        - Ram Jam and Wild Cherry - Black Betty; Play that funky music, 1997; SR-22130; Ram Jam; Wild Cherry (Box 404)
          Catalog # 49 78585; A-side Matrix # XSS 78585 A
          Epic
        - Ram Squad - Ballers (up in here) remixes, 2000; SR-22131; Ram Squad; E-Wreks (Box 404)
          Catalog # 012156249-1; A-side Matrix # 012156249-1-A
        - Ram Squad - Ballers (up in here), 2000; SR-22132; Ram Squad; Ereks XL (Box 404)
          Catalog # UNIR-20077-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20077-1A
        - Ram Squad - Ballers (up in here) remixes, 2000; SR-22133; Ram Squad; E-Wreks (Box 404)
        - Ram Trilogy - Titan EP (disc one), 2000; SR-22134; Ram Trilogy (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22135. Double album.
          Catalog # RAMM 28; A-side Matrix # RAMM 28 A
          RAM Records
          Essex, United Kingdom
        - Ram Trilogy - Titan EP (disc two), 2000; SR-22135; Ram Trilogy (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-22134. Double album.
          Catalog # RAMM 28; A-side Matrix # RAMM 28 C
        - Rama, Drew - Ectasy; Curb life; Ride, 2004; SR-22136; Rama, Drew (Box 404)
          Catalog # SIR0001; A-side Matrix # SOL0001A
          Soar International Records
          Lumberton, North Carolina
        - Ramazzotti, Eros - Occhi di speranza (remix), 1988; SR-22137; Ramazzotti, Eros (Box 404)
          Catalog # DDD 651507 6; A-side Matrix # CI-651507-1L-A
          DDD
          Italy
        - Ramm - Spark the universe, 1984; SR-22138; Ramm (Box 404)
          Catalog # CH84 12009; A-side Matrix # CH 12-84 A1
          Coach House
          Toronto, Canada
        - Ramocon, Phil - Take a trip, 1982; SR-22139; Ramocon, Phil (Box 404)
          Catalog # MLPS 7801; A-side Matrix # MLPS-7801-AS
        - Ramocon, Phil - Take a trip, 1982; SR-22140; Ramocon, Phil (Box 404)
        - Ramones - Subterranean jungle, 1983; SR-22141; Ramones (Box 404)
          Catalog # 1-23800; A-side Matrix # 1-23800 A-SH 1
          Sire
        - Rampage - We getz down, 1997; SR-22142; Rampage; 702 (Box 404)
          Catalog # ED 6060; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6060A-1
        - Rampage - We getz down, 1997; SR-22143; Rampage; 702 (Box 404)
        - Rampage - We getz down; Get the money and dip, 1997; SR-22144; Rampage; Busta Rhymes (Box 404)
          Catalog # ED 6051; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6051A-1
        - Rampage - We getz down; Get the money and dip, 1997; SR-22145; Rampage; Busta Rhymes (Box 404)
        - Rampage - Take it to the streets; Flipmode enemy #1, 1997; SR-22146; Rampage; Lawrence, Billy (Box 404)
          Catalog # ED-6032; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6032-A-1
        - Rampage the Last Boyscout - Wild for da night, 1996; SR-22147; Rampage the Last Boyscout (Box 404)
          Catalog # ED-5897; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5897-A1
        - Rampage the Last Boyscout - Beware of the rampsack, 1994; SR-22148; Rampage the Last Boyscout (Box 404)
          Catalog # RDP-5032; A-side Matrix # RDP-5032-SA SP1
          Rowdy Records
        - Ramsay, Lee - Out of da ville, 1998; SR-22149; Ramsay, Lee; Becky (Box 404)
          Catalog # RD 003; A-side Matrix # RD003A1
          Real Deal Records
          Nottingham, United Kingdom
        - Randell & Schippers - Let's go for it, 1986; SR-22150; Randell & Schippers (Box 404)
          Catalog # 4Z9 05995; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-05995-3AA
          Scotti Bros. Records
        - Randell & Schippers - Let's go for it, 1986; SR-23569; Randell & Schippers (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-23570. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # DB 1200; A-side Matrix # DB-1200-A
          Ear Candy Records
        - Fantasy - Let's go for it, 1986; SR-23570; Fantasy; Randell & Schippers (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-23569. Different discs.Promo
        - Random Source - Big stupid grin, 2003; SR-23571; Random Source (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-23572. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SOD002; A-side Matrix # 08 52402 20 1A1
          Sound of Disuye
        - Random Source - Big stupid grin, 2003; SR-23572; Random Source (Box 404)
          In same jacket as # SR-23571. 2 copies.
        - Randy & The Gypsys - Love you honey, 1989; SR-23573; Randy & The Gypsys (Box 404)
          Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # SP-12324; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012324A RE-1 ES1
        - Randyandy - The people (living in the U.S.A.), 1983; SR-23574; Randyandy (Box 404)
          Catalog # SP-17261; A-side Matrix # SP 017261A(RE-1)-ES1
        - Ranieri, Massimo - Perdere l'amore, 1988; SR-23575; Ranieri, Massimo (Box 404)
          Catalog # 24 2312-1; A-side Matrix # 242312-1 A
          WEA
          Milan, Italy
        - Ranjahz - Daily basis; Street life (daily basis remix), 1996; SR-23576; Ranjahz (Box 404)
          Catalog # PRO-7453-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-7453-0-A
          Profile Records
        - Rank and File - Sundown, 1982; SR-23577; Rank and File (Box 404)
          Catalog # 1-23833; A-side Matrix # 1-23833-A-SH6
          Slash
        - Rankin Don' - Real McCoy (Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!), 1995; SR-23578; Rankin Don' (Box 404)
          Catalog # KA 782-1; A-side Matrix # KA-782 A
          Kick Ass Records
        - Ranking, Copper - Friends, 1989; SR-23579; Ranking, Copper; Lee, Johnny (Box 405)
          Catalog # BMD 062; A-side Matrix # BMD-062-A1